Guide to the Gravity Probe B records SC1274
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Administrative records
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - APS Meeting - Jacksonville Florida, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Francis Everitt - Bio Presentations, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Fairbank workshop, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - T.E.U Rights Permissions, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Photo/image Licensing Requests, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Media Inquiries, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - NY Times Article, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - ABC Catalyst TV - GP-B story, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Mick Speen's GP-B movie, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - NASA Editorial Board Review, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Press Media Contacts, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Public Affairs EPO Presentations, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - GP-B Status Update, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - NASA GP-B Press Releases, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Stanford GP-B Press Releases, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - GP-B Results Announcement Plans, 2006 Nov/Dec-2007 Mar (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - MSFC - Steve Roy's GP-B Media/PR plan, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - NASA senior review of GP-B, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - GP-B Responses Queries [RTQ], undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - RTQ's, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Responses to Queries Info, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - GP-B Update - List Serve Problem Addresses, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Testing Einsteins Universe script, undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Stanford Video, undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Videofeedback Productions, undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Video Duplication, undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Video-taping service, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - GP-B Final Reports - Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - GP-B Science Report to NASA, undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - GP-B Final Report - Printing Distribution, undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - GP-B Animations, undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - New GP-B Website, undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Website Status Update, 2007 Summer (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - GP-B Webserver - Hi-Res Graphics Directory Contents, undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Drawings Artwork, undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Cryopump, undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Missing Inch, undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - GP-B Paper Model, undated (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Photo Proof Sheets, undated (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Launch Photo Prints, undated (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Photos, undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Launch Photo, undated (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Photo Collages, undated (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Spacecraft photos in orbit, undated (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - GP-B Poster Templates from APS, undated (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - PowerPoint Presentations, undated (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Telescope drawings, undated (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Resource Info DVD CD-ROM, undated (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - L-1 Web Casts, undated (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Content Sources for DVD CD-ROM, undated (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Launch Commemorative DVD, undated (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - PC Vector user's manual, 1995 Mar (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Programmer's manual, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - unlabeled, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - APU Supplement, Activity Report, 2001 Mar 22-Aug 17 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - APU Supplement, Activity Report, 2001 Mar 22-Aug 17 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - APU Supplement, Activity Report, 2001 Mar 22-Aug 17 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Gravity probe B experiment, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Data cleanup, 2004 Apr 10 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - testing page sizes 16K -> 4k, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Switchover PE2, 2004 Mar 11 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Switchover, 2003 Nov 21-Dec 10 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Sybase patch, 2003 Dec 5 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - transparency material unused, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - security course, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - L2- table corruption, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - 2005, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Maintenance, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Prod changes Audit trial, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - 2005, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Flash report, 1999 Aug 3 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Advanced aerospace, 1997 Oct 29 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - presentation GP-B, 2001 Jul 20 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - report, 1997 Jul 25 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - report, 2001 Jul 20 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - report, 2000 Jul 25 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - 1997, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - GPS, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - 1999, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Analysis of Spacecraft, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Summary report, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Spring 1989, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - GPS reciever papers, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - 1989 Oct 9-13, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - MATLAB, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - MATLAB, undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - green notebook, undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - MATLAB, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - MATLAB, undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - DBA Pdoc's Sdoc's AS-RUNs, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - 22H160 B/W, undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - unused transparency film, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Mathworks software install kit, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Global Positioning System, 1995 Jun 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - GPS software review, 1999 Oct 18 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - procedure, 1999 May 1 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Tensor development, 1997 Aug 8 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - articles, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - draft, 1999 Nov 21 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - article, 2000 Dec 20 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - unlabeled, 1996 Jan 25 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Activity Report, 2000 May - Sep 18 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - TANS vector, 1996 Nov 25 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - PC VECTOR, 1995 Nov (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - PC VECTOR, 1995 Nov (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - PC VECTOR, 1995 Nov (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - PC VECTOR, 1995 Nov (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - GPS subsystem critical design review 1, 1997 Nov 3 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - NASA training program student workbook, 1998 May (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Electrostatic Discharge Control, 1999 Jan 4 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Gravity Probe B program, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - testing, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Requirements for infant management, 2005 May 13 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - PAPERS, Cosmic Rad UV Photoemission, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - STEP presentation, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Cold Fusion, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Haish, Solar Flares, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - lambda point, Roger Williamson, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Field Emission, Supercond, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Guide Star, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - LT pressure measurement, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Superconductivity Aharonov Bohm, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Vacuum Sealants, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Remnant Magetization Cabrera, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Helmholtz coils, undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Cryopump, undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - GRS "wake" registry, 2005 May 13 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Award fees, 1998 Jan 13 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - untitled, 1997 Jan 10 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Step study, undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Experiment, undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - proof mass, undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - new cathode, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - new SCSo, undated (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Field Em. Cathode, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Proposal / SCSO, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - 15th award fee review, 1995 Oct-1996 Sep (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - third award fee review, 1995 Oct-1996 Sep (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Sasha Buchman Proposal Kickoff Meeting, 1994 Feb 3 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - LISA, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - NIAC, 1998 Jul 31 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - new Law field facility, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - ULF FSS, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 7th Pacific Coast gravity meeting, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - MG-8 (Marcel Grossman) The Technology Heritage of the Relativity Mission Gravity Probe B, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - MG-7 (Marcel Grossman) The Gravity Probe B Gyroscopes, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Moriond XXXII - Radiation Issues for Gravity Exp. In Space, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Moriond XV - A Low Temp. Gyroscope Clock for Gravitational Redshift Experiments, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Moriond XV- S C S O, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Moriond XIV - Applications of Superconductivity to Gravitational Exp. In Space, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - JPL 96 #2 workshop, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - JPL 96 #1 workshop, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - NASA/JPL, 1997 May (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - AAS/DDA 2000 Meeting Yosemite meeting (31st) Annual meeting, 2000 Apr 9-12 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - APS Mar meeting UV fiber by protons, 1995 Mar (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Asilomar - GP-B A test of gravitational theories, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - PPBWS/COSPAR, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Second Fairbank Conference Cosmic radiation issues for the GP-B Gyroscopes, by S. Buchman, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Second Fairbank Conference - GP-B Recent achievements and future developments, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - FPS 95 Gyroscope performance and Charge Control for the GP-B Relativity Mission, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - 22nd international Conference on Low Temperature. Helsinki, 1999 Aug (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - LISA, 1998 Jul (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - JPL Disturbance Reduction System, 1999 Jul 15 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Hellings, 1999 Sep 26 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - LISA; JPL, 1999 Jan (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Angular Resolution of Space-Based Detectors, 1999 Nov 1 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Rodrigues, Touboul, 1998 Jul (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - D. DeBra, 1999 Feb 25 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - correspondence, 1999 Mar 19 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - untitled, 1998 Nov 2 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - D. DeBra, 1999 Jan 23-30 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Excerpt, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Excerpt, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - LISA pamphlet, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Bill F., undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Space Science Enterprise Strategic Plan, 1997 Nov (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1998 Nov 16 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Buchman correspondence, 1998 Oct 15 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Robin Stevvins CV, undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - The Testbed Actuator, undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - LISA diagrams, undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - LISA, 1999 Mar (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - transparencies, undated (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - post-processed velocity accuracy, 2010 Oct 10 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Masters per antenna code, 2004 Aug 18 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Shestople GPS proton monitor, 2004 Aug 31 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Thermal Vacuum test procedure, 2000 Jun 8 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Code simulation testing, 2000 Nov 21 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Logic controller operator's manual, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - GPS reciever assembly, 2000 Mar 13 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Code simulation testing, 2000 Nov 21 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Thermal Vacuum test procedure, 2000 Jun 8 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - correspondence Carter Shestople, 2001 Feb 23 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - upgrade procedure, 2000 Jul 7 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Flight fabrication QA training, 1998 Aug 26 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Shipping notice Lockheed Martin, 2001 Aug 21 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - GPS signal generator requirements, 1995 Oct 20 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - TANS vector part inventory, 1998 May 7 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - TANS vector part inventory, 1998 May 18 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - TANS vector part inventory, 1998 May 7 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - TANS vector part inventory, 1998 May 20 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - TANS vector part inventory, 1998 May 19 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - post-processed positioning accuracy, 2000 Oct 10 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - EMI testing at Lockheed- Test report, 1999 Jan 11 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - GPS software review completion certificate, 2000 Aug 22 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - GPB LEO GMS, 2005 Aug 19 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Trimble final test procedure, 1996 Dec 11-13 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Procurement guidelines, 1994 Oct 10 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Lockheed Martin fax transmission, 1999 Aug 4 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - AA 272C Vol 1 custom course material, 1995 spring (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - data graphs, undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Antenna Receiver random vibration test, 1999 Jul 20 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - GSS Timeline reference data package, 2002 May 15 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - proton monitor, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Appendix Review no. 2, 1990 Jun 28 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Space vehicle system design verification and test plan, 2001 Dec 3 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - GIDL: Generalized Interference Detection and Localization System, 2002 Mar (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Photographs
  - GRAVITY PROBE-B IN PICTURES, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - G T U, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Gyroscopes, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Everitt, Francis, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Van Patten Anglim, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Student Negs, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Brad Pariciwson, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - John, Brad, Doron Science Illustrated, 1989 Apr (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Niobium Bird Appratus with Bird with Hiro Uematsu, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Bill Fairbank Photos, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Ted Ale Housing, 1989 Sep (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Taber at Datalog Monitor, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Barry at Microscope, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Picture of Yukinobu Miki Testing Squid in Screen Room, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - "Lo Van Ho Electronics", undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Jim Lockhart, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Picture of Jim Lockhart at Ultra-low Field Test Facility, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - PROBE, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Mike Condron w/ DC Squid and Dewar, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - GTU on SQUID package, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Gutt Probe, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Read-out, 1993 Mar 18 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - 92-3 SQUID Eletronics Unit, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - 92-4 Modular DC SQUID Electronics w/ sines, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - 92-2 Compact SQUID Electronics, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - 91-14 Readout Data Equip APS d.c Squid Electronics, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Read-out, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - NIST dc SQUID on SQUID Carrier, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Photomicrograph of Squid, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - 93-13 Chip Micrograph, 1993 Nov (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - 93-1 dc SQUIDS, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - 1. Gutt Kim Electronics; 2. Gutt Electronics, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Probe for dc SQUID Research, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Probe for dc SQUID Development, undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Read-out, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Staff, undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Telescope Chip, 1995 Jun 15 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Telescope Detector Chip, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Microchip, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Telescope, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Bonding Telescope to Quartz Block, 1994 Nov 18 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Telescope Room, 1992 Oct 27 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - GWO "6 PACK" Telescope Support, 1991 Aug (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Telescope, undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - 94-2 LMSC Helium Thruster Model, undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Chen Thruster, undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Thrusters, undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Transport, undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Woody Thesis Pix, undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - 94-1 Zhu Research, undated (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Black Hole Sculpture, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Artwork, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Metrology Lab, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 93-4 SimFlight(2) Lab, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Readout laboratory with tented clean room, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - MGP Integration, 1988 Jul (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - CLEAN Room - Gyros, etc., undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Facilities, Electronics and Varian, 1995 Aug 10 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Earthquake 1989, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Destruction of Stanford Physics tank, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - HEPL Hallway, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Loop Patterning Facility - Yellow Room, 1991 Aug (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - CLEAN ROOM - Bruce (color), 1988 Jul (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Fundamental Requirements, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 1991 Misc., undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Breakdown System, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Wet bench with fume hood, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Particulate Controlled Space Room 132, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Hardware Facilities in HEPL, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - CLEAN ROOM - Bruce (Black White) 2 views, 1988 Jul (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Facilities, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Space Vehicle Concepts, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Eucl view of telescope, 1997 Jun (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - SIA, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - GTU - 1 Final Integration Birdcage, 1995 Feb (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - New Dewar, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Payload, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Transport (Photos by Steve Castillo), 2001 Aug (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Photos by Mark Gottlieb, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Closeup of Ceramic Housing attached to Probe - GGTA, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Ceramic Gyro Housing Attached to Probe - GGT Facility, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Quartz Support Structure (GGTB), undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Gimballgo Gyro Test, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Birdcage Wiring, 1990 Jul (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Rat nest wiring, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Gate Valve, undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Leak Check of Probe, 1990 Feb (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - PROBE - in CLEANROOM, Vertical with TOPHAT, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Installation of QB flange bolts during probe integration, 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Preparing hook up of readout wires to SQVID, 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - QBA mounted in its precision manipulator, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - SIA Support Structure, Region of Probe showing spin-up lines after Gyro removal, undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Integrated support structure/ QBA on vertical manipulator in class 10 room, 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - SIA Region of Probe during integration of Squids, 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Connecting suspension cables during probe integration for FIST, 0 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Lowering support structure onto QBA during integration for FIST, 0 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Airlock of EDD during Probe Removal, 1991 Aug (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - MGP Set-up in Class 1000 Room During Functional tests, undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Close up of Probe during replacement of vacuum can - spin-up line plumbing for Gyroscope #1, undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Attaching bolts through QB Flange to fingers in support structure, undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Connecting suspension cables from gyroscope #2 to birdcage suspension connectors, undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Probe A, undated (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Probe B, undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - HEPL Detication, 1992 Aug (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Ping Charts, 1995 Dec (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Aerial Stanford, 1995 Sep 1 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - PA Airport, HEPL roof, hill, 1995 Aug 30 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Near-Far, 1995 Nov 30 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Pseudolite cards, 1994 Nov 13 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - 93-9. Pseudolite card Spectrum analyzer, undated (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - 93-8. Crow's landing, undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Roof Mem Aud, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - 92-5. GPS Roof Lab, undated (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - 93-3. GPS Antenna on Bottom of Piper Dakota, undated (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Todd Waas, 1996 Oct (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Pervan, others, 1996 Oct (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Airlock assembly lowered into DEWAR, undated (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Installation of Probe on Piston assembly, undated (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Operating valve Helium pre-cooling Transfer Line, undated (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Helium Transfers Mike Taber, undated (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - DATA, undated (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - SVA Series (D.H) 93-5, undated (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - SVA Series (Prints) 93-5, undated (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Lead Bag Expansion Rehearsal, 1988 Mar 22 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Ten inch lead bag removed from EDD during warm tests, 1991 Jun (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Removing miri-airlock during lead bag installation rehearsals, 1991 Jun (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - View of lead bag expanded in well of EDD, 1991 Jun (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - View of lead bag expanded in well of EDD, during warm rehearsals, 1991 Jun (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Window Vibration Tests, undated (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - dc Suspension System Bill Bencze (93-15), undated (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - UV Photon Production Measurement Equip (91-7), undated (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - A Commercial quadrant photodiode detector being tested, undated (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - QB Section with Bore for Gyro (91-1), undated (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - QB Section in Shake Test Fixture 91-2, undated (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Gyroscope installed in room temperature test facility, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - He binding energy test probe with DEWAR, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Test fixture for gyroscope caging symmulation, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Apparatus to study magnetic FLUX in Superconducting Films, undated (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Room temperature gyroscope test system RT-4, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Gyro mounted in room temp. test facility with vacuum can of, 1988 Oct 1 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Room temperature gyro test, undated (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Room temp gyro test sys. RT-4, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Commissioning tests of room temperature test system RT-3, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Gyroscope in FIST orientation installed in room temperature test system, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Early Gyro Testing, undated (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Test Instrument For Caging Assembly (91-5), undated (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Misc. Rotors, undated (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Sillicon Gyroscope - 1990 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Gyro parts in clean storage cabinet (8-91), 1991 Aug 1 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - LG Image of Single Crystal Rotor, undated (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - negs to organize, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - SCSO IE3/JPL, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - 6, undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - 4, undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - loose slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - QR, 1990 Feb (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - GP-B, undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - 1, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - SL-19 19th century apparatus, undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - housing in RT system, undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - GP-B, undated (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - 5, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - 3, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - 2, undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - GP-B, undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Ekta 200 Tsuchihashi, S., undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Step slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Alkemade, undated (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Alkemade, undated (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - GP-B, undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Alkemade, undated (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Removing vacuum can, undated (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Alkemade, undated (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Fire, 1989 Apr-May (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Quartz block on fingers index plate spaces, undated (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Alkemade, 1990 Aug (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Step slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - GP-B, undated (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Rotor housing, rotor in lapping, undated (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - QBA assembly, undated (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - unlabeled, undated (Box 16, Folder 66)